soleilselene.com 2012-11-20

# Privacy Policy │ Soleil Selene®

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Soleil Selene collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the http://www.soleilselene.com website.

### Your Personal Information

We collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. We collect the domain name and e-mail address (if entered) of users. However, users may visit our site anonymously.

### Cookies

This Site uses cookies to store visitor preferences and record user-specific information. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

### Third Party Sites

We may, occasionally, include links to third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Therefore, we take no responsibility and have no liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

### Changes to this Policy

The contents of this policy may be updated at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

If you have any questions regarding this policy, you may email us at leilani@soleilselene.com
